{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What are the core vaccines for a feline patient?",
      "answers": {
        "A": "Corona and FVRCP",
        "B": "Corona and FeLV",
        "C": "Rabies and FVRCP",
        "D": "Rabies and Influenza"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What parts of a patient's body should be restrained for a lateral exam?",
      "answers": {
        "A": "Just the ears",
        "B": "Head and Hind paws",
        "C": "Cute little Nose and Toes",
        "D": "Head and Front Paws"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the core vaccines for a canine patient?",
      "answers": {
        "A": "Rabies, DHLPP, Bordetella",
        "B": "Lepto, Lyme, Influenza",
        "C": "LPV, Lyme, Rabies",
        "D": "Rabies, CPV, Bordetella"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'FeLV'?",
      "answers": {
        "A": "Feline Licking Vaccine",
        "B": "Feral Less Violent",
        "C": "Fetal Lorax Virus",
        "D": "Feline Leukemia Virus"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'FIV'?",
      "answers": {
        "A": "Feline Immunodeficiency Virus",
        "B": "Fatal Intoxication Volume",
        "C": "Form Insulin Vaccine",
        "D": "Frightening Individual Vermin"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "A 4DX tests for the following:",
      "answers": {
        "A": "Heartworm, Lyme Disease, Ehrlicia and Leptosporosis",
        "B": "Leptosporosis, Lyme, Rabies and Parvovirus",
        "C": "Heartworm, Lyme Disease, Ehrlicia and Anaplasma",
        "D": "Rabies, Parvo, Kennel Cough and Cushings Disease"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "The client is the pet.",
      "answers": {
        "A": "True",
        "B": "False"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Exam rooms should be spot cleaned between each appointment.",
      "answers": {
        "A": "True",
        "B": "False"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a tiger top tube used for?",
      "answers": {
        "A": "Collecting whole blood to spin down for plasma.",
        "B": "Collecting whole blood to spin down for serum.",
        "C": "Shooting darts at fractious cats.",
        "D": "Distributing precise amounts of blood."
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "A client with no money is not a client at all.",
      "answers": {
        "A": "True",
        "B": "False",
        "C": "It depends on the severity of the patientâ€™s health"
      },
      "correctAnswerIndex": "2"
    }
  ]
}